[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "How would you describe the pain you usually have from your knee?",
    "answers": ["None", "Very mild", "Mild", "Moderate", "Severe"]
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Have you had any trouble with washing and drying yourself (all over) because of your knee?",
    "answers": ["No trouble at all", "Very little trouble", "Moderate troube", "Extreme difficulty", "Impossible to do"]
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Have you had any trouble getting in and out of a car or using public transport because of your knee? (whichever you would tend to use)",
    "answers": ["No trouble at all", "Very little trouble", "Moderate troube", "Extreme difficulty", "Impossible to do"]
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "For how long have you been able to walk before pain from your knee becomes severe? (with or without a stick)",
    "answers": ["No pain / More than 30 minutes", "16 to 30 minutes", "5 to 15 minutes", "Around the house only", "Not at all (severe pain when walking"]
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "After a meal (sat at a table), how painful has it been for you to stand up from a chair because of your knee?",
    "answers": ["Not at all painful", "Slightly painful", "Moderately painful", "Very painful", "Unbearable"]
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Have you been limping when walking, because of your knee?",
    "answers": ["Rarely / never", "Sometimes, or just at first", "Often, not just at first", "Most of the time", "All of the time"]
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Could you kneel down and get up again afterwards?",
    "answers": ["Yes, easily", "With little difficulty", "With moderate difficulty", "With  extreme difficulty", "No, impossible"]
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Have you been troubled by pain from your knee in bed at night?",
    "answers": ["No nights", "Only 1 or 2 nights", "Some nights", "Most nights", "Every nights"]
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "How much has pain from your knee interfered with your usual work(including housework)?",
    "answers": ["Not at all", "A little bit", "Moderately", "Greatly", "Totally"]
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Have you felt that your knee might suddenly 'give way' or let you down?",
    "answers": ["Rarely / never", "Sometimes, or just at first", "Often, not just at first", "Most of the time", "All of the time"]
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Could you do the household shopping on your own?",
    "answers": ["Yes, easily", "With little difficulty", "With moderate difficulty", "With  extreme difficulty", "No, impossible"]
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "infos": "During the past 4 weeks...",
    "question": "Could you walk down one flight of stairs?",
    "answers": ["Yes, easily", "With little difficulty", "With moderate difficulty", "With  extreme difficulty", "No, impossible"]
  }
]